var quiz = {
	question: "What color are coffee beans before they are roasted?"
	options: ['White', 'Brown', 'Green', 'Orange',],
	answer: "Green"
},
/*
	question: "On average, How many cups are consumed by Americans each day?"
	options: ['100 million'. '235 Million', '400 Million', '587 Million']
	answer: "400 Million"
},
{
	question: "What are the two main types of coffee beans?",
	options: ['Robusta and Augusta', 'Arabica and Aromatic', 'Caffeine and Green', 'Arabica and Robusta'],
	answer: "Arabica and Robusta"
},
{
	question: "Where does coffee originate from?"
	options: ['Columbia', 'Argentina', 'Hawaii', 'Ethiopia'],
	answer: 'Ethiopia'
},
{
	question: "What country is the leading coffee consumer?"
	options: ['Italy', 'United States', 'Italy', 'Columbia'],
	answer: "United States"
},
{
	question: "What country is most produced in?"
	options: ['Brazil', 'Nicaragua', 'El Salvador', 'Columbia']
	answer: "Columbia"
},
{
	question: "The worlds most expensive coffee is..."
	options: ['$60/lbs', '$120/lbs', '$270/lbs', '$600/lbs'],
	answer: "$600/lbs"
},
{
	question: "You would need to drink __ cups of coffee to overdose on Caffeine and die."
	options:[ 30, 57, 594, 100],
	answer:"100 cups"
},
{
	question: "Coffee stays warmer longer when you add?"
	options:['Cream', 'Sugar', 'Honey', 'Tea'],
	answer:"Cream"
},
{
	question:"The biggest cup of coffee ever brewed in 2014 in South Korea measured"
	options: ['300 Gallons', '500 Gallons', '80,000 Gallons', '3,700 Gallons']
	answer: "3,700 Gallons"
},
}
*/
var questionNumber = [];
var questionOptions = [];

